Dan Moldea investigative journalism collection, 1937-2008
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections Research Center
- Series 5: "Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer" research, 1962-2013; (5 boxes)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 7.2, 2000-2013 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 7.3, 2000-2013 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 7.4, 2000-2013 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 7.5, 2000-2013 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 7.6, 2000-2013 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 7.7, 2000-2013 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Washington Independent Writers - Reports to the WIW Bora of Directors from Dan E. Moldea, 1981-82 WIW President, 1981 - 1982 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Washington Independent Writers Documents, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 8.2, 2000-2013 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 8.3, 2000-2013 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 8.4, 2000-2013 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 8.5, 2000-2013 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 8.6, 2000-2013 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 8.7, 2000-2013 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 8.8, 2000-2013 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 8.9, 2000-2013 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 8.10, 2000-2013 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 8.11, 2000-2013 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 8.12, 2000-2013 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 9.1, 2000-2013 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 9.2, 2000-2013 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 9.3, 2000-2013 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 9.6, 2000-2013 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 9.7, 2000-2013 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 9.8, 2000-2013 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 9.9, 2000-2013 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 9.10, 2000-2013 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 9.11, 2000-2013 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 10.1, 2000-2013 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 10.2, 2000-2013 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 10.3, 2000-2013 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 10.4, 2000-2013 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 10.5, 2000-2013 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 10.8, 2000-2013 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 10.9, 2000-2013 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 10.10, 2000-2013 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 11.1, 2000-2013 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 11.2, 2000-2013 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 11.3, 2000-2013 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 11.4, 2000-2013 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 11.5, 2000-2013 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 11.6, 2000-2013 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 11.7, 2000-2013 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 11.8, 2000-2013 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 11.9, 2000-2013 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 11.10, 2000-2013 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 11.11, 2000-2013 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 11.13, 2000-2013 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 12.3, 2000-2013 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 12.4, 2000-2013 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 12.5, 2000-2013 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 12.6, 2000-2013 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 12.7, 2000-2013 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 12.9, 2000-2013 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 12.10, 2000-2013 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 12.11, 2000-2013 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 12.12, 2000-2013 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 12.13, 2000-2013 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 13.1, 2000-2013 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 13.2, 2000-2013 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 13.3, 2000-2013 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 13.4, 2000-2013 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 14.1, 2000-2013 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 14.2, 2000-2013 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 14.3, 2000-2013 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 14.4, 2000-2013 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 14.5, 2000-2013 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 14.6, 2000-2013 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 14.7, 2000-2013 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 14.8, 2000-2013 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 14.9, 2000-2013 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 15.1, 2000-2013 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 15.2, 2000-2013 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 16.1, 2000-2013 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 16.2, 2000-2013 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 16.3, 2000-2013 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 16.4, 2000-2013 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 16.6, 2000-2013 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 16.7, 2000-2013 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 16.8, 2000-2013 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 17.1, 2000-2013 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 17.2, 2000-2013 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Final Draft 8, 2000-2013 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 18.1, 2000-2013 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 18.2, 2000-2013 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 18.3, 2000-2013 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 18.4, 2000-2013 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 19.1, 2000-2013 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 19.2, 2000-2013 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 19.2a, 2000-2013 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 19.3, 2000-2013 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 19.4, 2000-2013 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 19.5, 2000-2013 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 19.5a, 2000-2013 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 19.6, 2000-2013 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 20.1, 2000-2013 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 20.2, 2000-2013 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 20.4, 2000-2013 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 20.6, 2000-2013 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 20.7, 2000-2013 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 20.8, 2000-2013 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 20.9, 2000-2013 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 21.1, 2000-2013 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 21.2, 2000-2013 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 21.3, 2000-2013 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 21.4, 2000-2013 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 22.1, 2000-2013 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 22.1a, 2000-2013 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 22.2, 2000-2013 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 22.3, 2000-2013 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Confessions of a Guerrilla Writer - Chapter 22.4, 2000-2013 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Series 6: "The Hunting of Cain" research, 1977-1981; (1 box)
  - The Hunting of Cain - Newspaper Copies and Product Info, 1977, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - The Hunting of Cain - Chapter One, August 11, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - The Hunting of Cain - Chapter Two, August 11, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - The Hunting of Cain - Chapter Three, August, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - The Hunting of Cain - Chapter Four, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - The Hunting of Cain - Chapter Five, August, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - The Hunting of Cain - Chapter Six, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - The Hunting of Cain - Chapter Seven, August, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - The Hunting of Cain - Chapter Eight, August, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - The Hunting of Cain - Chapter Nine, August, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - The Hunting of Cain - Chapter Ten, August, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - The Hunting of Cain - Chapter Eleven, October, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - The Hunting of Cain - Chapter Twelve, August, October, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - The Hunting of Cain - Chapter Thirteen, August - September, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - The Hunting of Cain - Chapter Fourteen, August - September, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - The Hunting of Cain - Chapter Fifteen, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - The Hunting of Cain - Chapter Sixteen, August - October, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - The Hunting of Cain - Chapter Seventeen, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - The Hunting of Cain - Chapter Eighteen, August - December, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - The Hunting of Cain - Chapter Nineteen, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - The Hunting of Cain - Chapter Twenty, August - December, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - The Hunting of Cain - Chapter Twenty - One, 1980 - 1981 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - The Hunting of Cain - Chapter Twenty - Two, 1980 - 1981 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - The Hunting of Cain - Chapter Twenty - Three, 1980 - 1981 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - The Hunting of Cain - Chapter Twenty - Four, 1980 - 1981 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - The Hunting of Cain - Chapter Twenty - Five, 1980 - 1981 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - The Hunting of Cain - Chapter Twenty - Six, 1980 - 1981 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - The Hunting of Cain - Chapter Twenty - Seven, 1980 - 1981 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - The Hunting of Cain - Chapter Twenty - Eight, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - The Hunting of Cain - Chapter Twenty - Nine, 1980 - 1981 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - The Hunting of Cain - Epilogue, 1980 - 1981 (Box 15, Folder 31)